EJ WILLARD

CONTACT

0430 617 770

ellijayne.m.willard@gmail.com
Portfolio: https://ellijayne.github.io

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Web Development: 2018

Western Sydney University

B.A. Social Sciences (Criminology & Laws)

SKILLS

Ember JS

JavaScript

Semantic HTML | Handlebars

CSS | PostCSS | Sass

Postman

Git | Bitbucket | Source Tree

Ingesting RESTful APIs

BEM Methodology

PostgreSQL

Responsive Web Design

Ruby on Rails

REFERENCES

References available on request

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a creative Web Developer with a background in the legal profession. My professional experience has taught me discipline and how important continuous learning is, which I feel really jives well with the tech world. The most exciting part about this change is being able to use my creativity, there is no better feeling than seeing your work come to life in the browser.

I also love the diversity of talent that the tech world attracts and am looking forward to working with an innovative company that has a fantastic culture!

EXPERIENCE

Jaxsta

October 2019 - present || Front End Web Developer

At Jaxsta, I have been afforded the opportunity to work across several departments and get stuck into all aspects of the product.

I have written production code for the front-end application, jumped into the Postgres database, worked with third parties on the integration of their APIs into our product and worked closely with the design team to bring their designs to life.

General Assembly

August 2019 - November 2019 || Instructional Assistant (Contract)

In this role I was assisting students with problem solving and learning HTML, CSS and JavaScript for GA's 10 week part-time Front-end Web Development course.

Squiz

October 2018 to Present || Junior Web Developer

At Squiz I was able to work across various projects for numerous government departments. The most notable project I was the sole developer on was the integration of three new API endpoints for the improvement of an exisiting government price comparison site.

General Assembly

June 2018 to August 2018 || Web Development Immersive Student

Major projects include:

- > Kana-o-Manabu: Japanese Language Learning App https://kana-manabu.herokuapp.com
- > Audiophiles: Music/Vinyl Database https://audiophiles.herokuapp.com
- > Meet You: Dating App https://todo-meetyou.herokuapp.com

Hunt & Hunt Lawyers

May 2016 - June 2018 || Paralegal

I worked on the Defendant side of Personal Injury Claims. Provided primary support for Senior Counsel & Partners. Managing competing interests of clients and constantly negotiating with different stakeholders to obtain the right outcome for them. The role involved keeping on top of the constant legislative changes and new case law that impacted upon the cases we were running.

Slater & Gordon Lawyers

March 2015 - May 2016 || Senior Legal Assistant